This hairstyle is becoming very viral these days.
So, I thought why not
try it too.  For this we
need a lot of rubber bands, so I have taken this
and will partition my hair into two and put
it behind.  Then we will move
a little hair forward from both sides so that we
can put a rubber band in it.  So look at this and
moving it a little higher we have to put a rubber band
so that the design is made well.  And then the same
process has to be followed again.  You have to take hair from here
and hair from there.  And
put a rubber band here.  Then
we have to repeat the same process again.  You have to take some hair
from here and apply rubber on this hair
and then take it from here.  I have to
put it in that one.  I don't know whether I am able to
explain it well to you people
or not.  You will understand more after watching it.
So just do the entire hair in this manner.
And finally,
when your hair at the back is finished, then
you should put a rubber band in the remaining hair
so that it looks good from the back.  So here
I have put a rubber band and will
inflate it a little so that it looks good.
And now comes the turn to move the hair back, that is, to
see the result.  So
look, this is the hairstyle I have created.
By the way, his hair was not curly.  My hair
is straight so you might not like the design a little.
Well,
I have made this hairstyle for the first time, so I think
I have given my best, but
I made one mistake, I should
not have worn this dress, then this hairstyle would have looked
better, ok bye, see you
in the next video.